Usman Tahir Siddiqui

+966 57 061 6739

 \vee

usman.tsidd@gmail.com

Director & Videographer

Digital Videographer offering 5 years of relevant experience and true to creative goals. Strong attention to detail and accuracy, exceptional communication skills and the important ability to work alone or with a team. Able to provide quality artistic direction to attain desired results.

Experience

Social Media Head

Turnstile Inc. 2020-Present

DOP & Director

S2S Marketing 2021

Videographer

Rocket Science Studios 2018-Present

Assistant Director

starstruck Films 2021

Accomplishments

- Nikon Training School -Ranked top ten in class (Middle East - 2009)
- Manual lens adjustment accuracy
- Lead Photographer for Media Society, **COMSATS University**
- Lead Photographer for Media Society, **SZABIST**

Education

SZABIST University

BS in Media Sciences

2019 - 2023

- · Founding Member of the Film Society
- Vice-President of the Adventure Club
- Staff Member of the Student Council

Comsats University

Courses in Biotech & Bioinfo

2017 - 2019

Pakistan International School (Matriculation and Fsc.)

2015-2017

- Most Co-operative Alumni Awardee
- Member of the Editorial Board
- Vice President of the Conservation Club
- Member of the Photo Team

Skills and Abilities

- Strong Compositional Skills
- Nikon and Canon Expert
- Ability to Improvise
- Problem Solving Skills
- Communication Skills"
- · Proficient in 3 Languages (English, Urdu, and conversational Arabic)